allurebridals.com 2018-06-29

# Allure Bridals | Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.allurebridals.com and Allure Bridals, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Allure Bridals, Inc. include www.allurebridals.com, Allure Bridals, Inc., Madison James, www.madison-james.com and www.madisonjamesbridal.com. The Allure Bridals, Inc. website is a wedding and prom fashion site. By using the Allure Bridals, Inc. website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

#### Collection of your Personal Information 

Allure Bridals, Inc. may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. Allure Bridals, Inc. may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, household income and Wedding Planning Information. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. 

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Allure Bridals, Inc.. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Allure Bridals, Inc. website. 

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Allure Bridals, Inc.'s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. 

Allure Bridals, Inc. encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Allure Bridals, Inc. so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Allure Bridals, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Allure Bridals, Inc. website. 

#### Use of your Personal Information 

Allure Bridals, Inc. collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. Allure Bridals, Inc. may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Allure Bridals, Inc. and its affiliates. Allure Bridals, Inc. may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. 

Allure Bridals, Inc. does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. 

Allure Bridals, Inc. may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is transferred to the third party. Allure Bridals, Inc. may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Allure Bridals, Inc., and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

Allure Bridals, Inc. may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Allure Bridals, Inc., in order to determine what Allure Bridals, Inc. services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Allure Bridals, Inc. to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. 

Allure Bridals, Inc. will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Allure Bridals, Inc. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Allure Bridals, Inc.; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Allure Bridals, Inc., or the public. 

#### Use of Cookies 

The Allure Bridals, Inc. website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Allure Bridals, Inc. pages, or register with Allure Bridals, Inc. site or services, a cookie helps Allure Bridals, Inc. to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Allure Bridals, Inc. website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Allure Bridals, Inc. features that you customized. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Allure Bridals, Inc. services or websites you visit. 

#### Security of your Personal Information 

Allure Bridals, Inc. secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

#### Children Under Thirteen 

Allure Bridals, Inc. does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

#### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Allure Bridals, Inc. by contacting us here: \- Web page: <http://www.allurebridals.com/profile/edit/>

#### Changes to this Statement 

Allure Bridals, Inc. will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Allure Bridals, Inc. encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Allure Bridals, Inc. is protecting your information. 

Effective as of May 21, 2014
